<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<QuestDescription>
    <QuestCaptionName 
	linMasFinalQuest="Defeat Danny Boy at his own game"
	linMasTraining="Training"
	linMasBugInTheSystem="Bugs In The System" 
	linMasPickAFaction="Pick A Faction" 
	linMasMoreBugsInTheSystem="More Bugs In The System"  
	linMasTheRatScuttle="The Rat Scuttle"
	linMasWhoIsEscaping="Who is Escaping?"

	johnny666Rep="Johnny666 Rep Quest"
	johnny66680Rep="Johnny666 80 Rep Quest"
	johnny666CheatALittle="Cheat A Little"
	johnny666TrainingDone="Johnny666 Training Done"

	geminiThePrideOfJolly="The Pride of Jolly"
	geminiKnockEmOut="Knock Em Out"
	geminiKeyToThePlan="Key To The Plan"
	geminiTalkToTheSword="Talk To The Sword"
	
	jollyTwoPendants="Two Pendants"
	jollyKnockEmOut="Knock Em Out"
	jollyKeyToThePlan="Key To The Plan"
	jollyTalkToTheSword="Talk To The Sword"
	
	santosoKeyToThePlan="Key To The Plan"
	santosoTalkToTheSword="Talk To The Sword"/>

    <Description 
	linMasPickAFaction="Speak with either Jolly or the Gemini 

Twins to align yourself with a faction. 

Choose wisely." 
	
	linMasBugInTheSystem="Make your way to the cafeteria and 

proceed to kill ten cockroaches. Return 

to Lin Ma when you have completed this 

task." 
	
	linMasMoreBugsInTheSystem="Make your way to the cafeteria and  

proceed to kill twenty cockroaches again. 

Return to Lin Ma when you have completed 

this task."  
	
	linMasTheRatScuttle="Make your way to the cafeteria and 

proceed to kill twenty rats. Return 

to Lin Ma when you have completed this 

task."
	
	linMasWhoIsEscaping="Figure out who is making the escape 

plans and report back to Lin Ma."
	
	linMasTraining="Speak to Johnny666 to use the training 

grounds and prepare for the fight to 

come."
	linMasFinalQuest="Show up at the Arena and prepare for the 

final Fight."
	
	jollyTalkToTheSword="Find Santoso and speak with him about 

the Skeleton Key."

	jollyKeyToThePlan="Report back to Jolly about your meeting 

with Santoso."
	
	jollyTwoPendants="Sneak into the Gemini Twin's cell and 

steal the pendants from them, Return to 

Jolly after."
	
	jollyKnockEmOut="Train up at Johnny666, find the Gemini 

Twins after you've completed the this 

task."
	
	geminiTalkToTheSword="Find Santoso and speak with him about 

the Skeleton Key."

	geminiKeyToThePlan="Report back to the twins about your 

meeting with Santoso."

	geminiKnockEmOut="Train up at Johnny666, find Jolly after 

you've completed the this task."

	geminiThePrideOfJolly="Sneak into Jolly's cell and steal 

the earring from him. Return to Jolly 

after."
	
	johnny666CheatALittle="Retrieve a bottle of steroids and bring 

it back to Johnny666."/>
	<ItemDescription 
		Cigarettes="A necessary addiction. 5 cigarettes can be 

exchanged with the faction leader for $1 in cash." 
		
		SteroidSyringe="Boosts muscle power and provides extraordinary 

strength. This item when used gives you 3 

exercise points." 
		
		Soap="This item is used to make an imprint of the Cell 

Block Key. Make sure not to drop it in the shower." 		
		
		SoapMould="The bar of soap molded with an imprint of the 

Cell Block Key. Give this item to Santoso to 

make copies of the key." 
		
		OfficeKey="This is the key to Lin Ma's office." 

		CellBlockKey="This key unlocks all the cells. Make sure you 

use it stealthily." 
		
		PainKillers="Blocks out the pain. This item heals the player 

in the arena while in combat (you can only have 

one of these in your inventory at all times)." 
		
		Money="Cold hard cash. Used to purchase items from 

Santoso's store." 
		
		Pendant="A priceless treasure of Terrence and Dougie 

Stalls (The Gemini Killers)." 
		
		Earring="Jolly's pride and joy. Rumors say that Jolly 

ripped it of a popstar's ear after he murdered her." 		

		Cockroach="This filthy infestation of bugs can be found in 

the cafeteria. Good thing they're high in protein." 		

		Rat="This rodent menace is found in the cafeteria. 

Try not to catch the bubonic plague."/>
</QuestDescription>